http://www.lillypad.com.au/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy | Lilly Pad
Account
Login
Register
Cart:
Send Flowers Online +
BirthdayCongratulationsNew BabyRomanceSympathyThank YouInterflora Australia Wide
PRIVACY POLICY
1. WHAT INFORMATION DOES LILLYPAD FLOWERS GATHER/TRACK ABOUT YOU?
The www.lillypad.com.au site collects general information on visitors to this site through the web site statistics sent to the server when you request a page on the Internet. This site does not ask for any personally identifying information such as name or company.
This site contains links to other sites. www.lillypad.com.au is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.
2. WHAT DOES LILLYPAD FLOWERS DO WITH THE INFORMATION IT GATHERS/TRACKS?
Demographic and profile data is not used other than presenting on the site and helping to target the types of information and content included on the site.
www.lillypad.com.au will not sell, barter or trade your personal information gathered at the time of sign up, except where noted above, and/or when required by law to protect the safety of members, employees or property. Any information that you supply in reference to an advertisement posted on www.lillypad.com.au or outside marketing campaign in conjunction with an advertisement is not protected under this privacy policy.
3. WHAT SECURITY MEASURES ARE IN PLACE?
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All registration information is stored in secure locations on a password protected computer.
4. CAN VISITORS CHOOSE TO OPT-OUT OR CHANGE PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Lillypad Flowers
Melbourne florist delivering bespoke floral gifts, Interflora flowers Australiawide and providing unique special event and wedding flowers.
277 Spring StreetReservoirVictoria Australia 3073lillypad@interfloraflorist.com.au
Connect With Us
Lillypad Flowers
2020 | powered by flowerstoreInABox™
